# Kluka Kate

Mobile: +65 9059 1693 | Email: klukakatarzyna@gmail.com |

Address: 5A Lorong How Sun 536563 Singapore



I am an operations specialist who possesses a robust understanding of financial services management through close working across divisions and developing strong client-focused relationships. Several years of the financial experience with corporate actions, equities, fixed income, futures, options and swaps and complex financial instruments. Able to work under pressure and extra hours to ensure timely project completion.

# **Professional experience**

### **State Street - Senior Hedge Fund Accountant (Associate 2)**

May 2017 - November 2017

#### **Calculation of Fund Net Asset Value:**

- Calculate the value of the fund's assets (net asset value and gross asset value) and analyze it according to the market value (experience with corporate actions, equities, fixed income, futures, options and swaps and complex financial instruments)
- Ensure controls are in place and accounts are accurate on a daily basis, providing clear and accurate management information to support decision-making
- Handle accounting for assigned complex funds, including review of daily price control checks, P&L reasonableness
- Reviews and verifies completed Net Asset Value performed by other Fund Accountants (with the NAV accuracy goal being 100%) in accordance with agreed timelines
- Monitors, proves, and reviews for reasonability the Fund valuation components.

#### **Reconciliation – Accounting related:**

- Manage and maintain the hedge fund accounts
- Prepare cash and currency reconciliations to all counterparty accounts for each assigned fund ensuring that reconciling items are investigated and resolved, or escalated in a timely manner
- Reconciliation and verification of all subscription and redemption activity
- Reviews account balances per trial balance to account balances per subsidiary ledgers resolve differences where required, assists and provides direction to staff in resolving discrepancies
- Calculate and process income and expense accruals including fee calculations and trading accruals
- Review, sign and date fund accounting checklist when required
- Assists where required in preparing monthly reports, and reviews reports prepared by team
- · Assists in preparation and review of client-specific reports, management reports and other information requirements
- Identify exceptions and problems affecting accounting records and prices, communicating same to management, and assisting in their resolution.

# Assist in maintenance and improvement of systems applications:

- Coordinate with data/operational teams to ensure data/methodology/operations are in place to support products and fund analysis requirements.
- Identify potential risks and take initiatives to reduce risk and enhance efficiency of the fund

#### **Euroclear Bank - Corporate Actions Analyst**

## **Reconciliation – Accounting related:**

- Reconciling cash and securities movements
- Manage and maintain the client's accounts
- Manage accounting functions including maintenance of accounts payable, accounts receivable; ensures accuracy and timeliness
- Performing day to day financial transactions, including verifying, classifying
- Monitoring customer account details for non-payments, delayed payments and other irregularities
- Ensuring that queries, exceptions and reconciliation discrepancies are investigated and resolved appropriate follow-up (timely, accurately)
- Facilitate payments by sending bill reminders and contacting clients
- Follow up payment and distribution of entitlement to client accounts act as escalation point to ensure any issues are resolved in a timely manner

#### **Corporate Actions related:**

- Monitoring and booking the corporate actions :
  - voluntary e.g repurchase offer, dividend Reinvestment Plan (DRIP), rights Issue, Dutch Auction, AGM / EGM proxy voting on shareholders meetings
  - mandatory e.g. stock splits, dividend issues, mergers and acquisitions, and spinoffs
  - mandatory with choice e.g. cash Stock Option, Merger with Elections
- Accurately and timely treating the lifecycle of transactions and/or events
- Summarizes current financial status by collecting information, preparing balance sheet, profit and loss statement, and other reports

#### Client's related:

- Interacting with local market institutions and/or agents (all over the world) to collect information and investigate discrepancies.
- Monitoring customer's account activities Reconciling and processing queries regarding client's accounts (including collection accounts) and incoming / outgoing payments
- Supporting client services to solve customer's issues/requests phone and written
- Understanding of and experience in processing ISO15022 SWIFT messages/EUCLID/EasyWay handle cancellations and amendments of instructions
- Keeping your relationships aware of all new services and changes that impact their activity with Euroclear Bank

#### BNP Paribas - Assistant Advisor to Corporate&Transaction Banking

August 2014 - June 2015

#### **Reconciliation – Accounting related:**

- Understanding of Accounts Payable and Receivable processes
- Set invoices up for payment, enter and upload invoices into accounting software
- Responsible for all accounting work necessary to insure accounts payable are processed in a timely and efficient
  manner
- Monitors account balances and related financial activity for the purpose of ensuring that allocations are accurate and complying with established financial practices
- Facilitate payments by sending bill reminders and contacting clients
- Generate and send monthly Customer Account Statements to customers and other internal parties if required
- Supplier statement reconciliation if required
- Prepare and process electronic transfers and payments wire transfer payment requests

#### Client's related:

- Active support of the ongoing work of Relationship Manager
- Interpret profit and loss data and balance sheet information supporting Senior Analysts
- Monitor and analyse client's revenue and profitability on a regular basis (by location and by product), ensuring
  financial performance is achieved through delivery of long term and profitable revenue streams, taking actions to
  maintain and improve contribution
- Responsible for the proper circulation of the documentation related to client's activities i.e. invoices etc.
- Know the client and the client's requirements responsible for clients' "Know Your Client" policy and procedures
- Seek out new customers and developing existing relationships with the current customer base
- Intermediation between corporate clients and other bank's units in order to solve any difficulties

<sup>&</sup>quot;I hereby give consent for my personal data to be processed for the purposes of recruitment, in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act dated 29.08.1997 (uniform text:Journal of Laws of the Republic of Poland 2002 No 101, item 926 with further amendments)"

- Assisting in the day-to-day running of the Accounts Office, active support for team in the current duties
- Provide administrative assistance and support –generate and send out invoices
- Reconciling vendor statements
- Maintain filing and invoice monitoring systems
- Maintains Accounts Payable aging and corresponding accounts payable files
- Verification and reconciliation of accounts, agreeing settlements
- Assisting with month-end closing
- Analysis and the introduction of internal and external documents to the accounting system
- Send reminder letters for overdue accounts
- Preparation of statements and reports in Excel

## **Voluntary Work**

### Project Manager Festival of Business "BOSS" Business Centre Club

December 2012 - April 2013

- Coordinating a team of 10 people management project team
- Planning and implementation of the project strategy and project activities
- Preparation of project documentation (taking care of invoices etc.)
- Making progress reports for management
- Complete budget management, establishing cooperation in the framework of a possible funding from government agencies
- Preparation of the budget and the required documents,
- Monitoring activities and ensuring the efficiency of processes

#### Education

### **Cracow University of Economics**

2010 - 2015

- Finance and Accounting | Majoring in Business Finance Master Degree
- Economics and International Relations | Majoring in Economics Bachelor's Degree

# **Skills & Certifications**

- Basic Project Management certificate
- Knowledge of Lotus Notes
- Certificate Ernst & Young Academy of Business Advanced Corporate Actions
- London Chamber of Commerce and Industry Certificate English For Business C1
- London Chamber of Commerce and Industry Course English Accounting C1
- ISTQB International Software Testing Qualification at the Foundation Level
- Murex Platform

## **Miscellaneous information**

- Languages: English Advanced, both written and spoken (C1)
- Technical skills: Fluent at MS Office especially Microsoft Excel
- Bloomberg
- Salesforce

Availability: immediate